const questionBank = {
    'A': [
        { "question": "U.S. state where the Ozarks are located", "correctAnswers": ["Arkansas"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country with the Saharan oasis city of Tamanrasset", "correctAnswers": ["Algeria"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Capital known as the White Marble City", "correctAnswers": ["Ashgabat"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "European country home to Innsbruck", "correctAnswers": ["Austria"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Largest state in Brazil", "correctAnswers": ["Amazonas"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital of Turkiye", "correctAnswers": ["Ankara"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Dutch city known for its canals and Museum District", "correctAnswers": ["Amsterdam"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "US state with the most lakes", "correctAnswers": ["Alaska"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "State capital of New York", "correctAnswers": ["Albany"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Small landlocked country between France and Spain", "correctAnswers": ["Andorra"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "City where the Taj Mahal is located", "correctAnswers": ["Agra"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country home to kangaroos and the Sydney Opera House ", "correctAnswers": ["Australia"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country home to Lionel Messi", "correctAnswers": ["Argentina"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state on the Gulf of Mexico", "correctAnswers": ["Alabama"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Largest continent in the world", "correctAnswers": ["Asia"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Most populous continent in the world", "correctAnswers": ["Asia"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Continent with the highest population of Penguins", "correctAnswers": ["Antarctica"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Ocean separating North America and Europe", "correctAnswers": ["Atlantic", "Atlantic Ocean"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Continent home to the Sahara Desert", "correctAnswers": ["Africa"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in South America with Patagonia and Buenos Aires", "correctAnswers": ["Argentina"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "City in Arkansas where Walmart is headquartered nearby", "correctAnswers": ["Arkadelphia"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
    ],
    'B': [
        { "question": "State in northeast Brazil", "correctAnswers": ["Bahia"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country in South Asia known as the Land of the Thunder Dragon", "correctAnswers": ["Bhutan"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Body of water between India and Myanmar", "correctAnswers": ["Bay of Bengal", "Bengal Bay"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Large port city in South Korea's southeast", "correctAnswers": ["Busan"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Peninsula in northwest Mexico", "correctAnswers": ["Baja California", "Baja"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "City and province in Catalonia", "correctAnswers": ["Barcelona"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Adriatic port city of over 300k", "correctAnswers": ["Bari"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Largest country in South America", "correctAnswers": ["Brazil"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Capital of Germany", "correctAnswers": ["Berlin"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country known worldwide for their waffles", "correctAnswers": ["Belgium"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Tallest building in the world", "correctAnswers": ["Burj Khalifa"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Landlocked country in South America", "correctAnswers": ["Bolivia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Montana's Magic City", "correctAnswers": ["Billings"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Strait in between The Black Sea and The Mediterannean", "correctAnswers": ["Bosphorus", "Bosporos"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Port city in Massachusetts and home to the Celtics", "correctAnswers": ["Boston"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Capital of Thailand", "correctAnswers": ["Bangkok"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Canadian national park located south of Jasper", "correctAnswers": ["Banff"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Zone within St. Paul's Bay in the Northern Region of Malta", "correctAnswers": ["Bugibba"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Popular tourist resort located on the southern Aegean coast of Turkey", "correctAnswers": ["Bodrum"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
    ],
    'C': [
        { "question": "Capital of Venezuela", "correctAnswers": ["Caracas"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country home to Chengdu, Chongqing, and Changchun", "correctAnswers": ["China"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Japanese city and prefecture east of Tokyo", "correctAnswers": ["Chiba"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Massive geological region encircling Hudson Bay", "correctAnswers": ["Canadian Shield"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Largest city of Wales", "correctAnswers": ["Cardiff"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Ecuadorian mountain whose peak is the farthest point from Earth's center", "correctAnswers": ["Chimborazo"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Largest island in the Middle East", "correctAnswers": ["Cyprus"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Greek island that is the birthplace of Zeus", "correctAnswers": ["Crete"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country with the longest coastline", "correctAnswers": ["Canada"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where Hollywood and The Golden Gate Bridge is located", "correctAnswers": ["California"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Most Populous U.S. state", "correctAnswers": ["California"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Second largest country in the world by area", "correctAnswers": ["Canada"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Landlocked country in Africa", "correctAnswers": ["Chad"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "US state with the nickname \”Constitution State\”", "correctAnswers": ["Connecticut"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country with the driest non-polar desert in the world ", "correctAnswers": ["Chile"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country with the largest population of pink dolphins", "correctAnswers": ["Colombia"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Capital of Egypt", "correctAnswers": ["Cairo"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Asian Country with the second largest population in the world", "correctAnswers": ["China"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Latin American country with no standing army", "correctAnswers": ["Costa Rica", "Curacao"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "US City with the nickname \”Windy City\”" , "correctAnswers": ["Chicago"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Landlocked country in Africa", "correctAnswers": ["Chad"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country where Paradise by Coldplay music video was filmed ", "correctAnswers": ["South Africa"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Island where Crab Rave was recorded", "correctAnswers": ["Christmas Island"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "City in France that hosted the first Winter Olympics", "correctAnswers": ["Chamonix"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },

    ],
    'D': [
        { "question": "City with the tallest building in the world", "correctAnswers": ["Dubai"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Southernmost country in Scandinavia", "correctAnswers": ["Denmark"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Capital of the Emerald Isle", "correctAnswers": ["Dublin"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country and capital in the Horn of Africa", "correctAnswers": ["Djibouti"], "difficulty": "hard"},
        { "question": "Largest city of South Africa's Garden Province", "correctAnswers": ["Durban"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country with the second most MLB players", "correctAnswers": ["Dominican Republic"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in the US with the first paved road", "correctAnswers": ["Detroit"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Famous alps located in Northern Italy", "correctAnswers": ["Dolomites", "The Dolomites"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Indian city with the largest spice market in Asia", "correctAnswers": ["Delhi"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Small city in Newfoundland and Labrador known for its unusual name", "correctAnswers": ["Dildo"], "difficulty": "grandmaster"},
        { "question": "Capital city located in Dominica", "correctAnswers": ["Roseau"], "difficulty": "hard"},
        { "question": "Capital city located in Senegal", "correctAnswers": ["Dakar"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Second largest country in Africa by area", "correctAnswers": ["Democratic Republic of the Congo", "DRC"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Largest city on the island of Bali", "correctAnswers": ["Denpasar"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Highest point in the United States", "correctAnswers": ["Denali"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "National Park where the lowest elevation in the U.S. is located", "correctAnswers": ["Death Valley"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in Ireland famous for Guinness", "correctAnswers": ["Dublin"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. state capital that is exactly one mile high", "correctAnswers": ["Denver"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Capital city of the historical Burgundy region in eastern France", "correctAnswers": ["Dijon"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },



        
    ],
    'E': [
        { "question": "Only African country with Spanish as its official language", "correctAnswers": ["Equatorial Guinea"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country formerly known as Swaziland", "correctAnswers": ["Eswatini"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Mongolia's second largest city", "correctAnswers": ["Erdenet"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "South African province home to Bhisho", "correctAnswers": ["Eastern Cape"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Greatest first name of all time", "correctAnswers": ["Eric"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Onion capital of the US", "correctAnswers": ["Eagan", "Elko"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Country with the Pyramids of Giza", "correctAnswers": ["Egypt"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country whose capital city is nicknamed \”New Rome\” ", "correctAnswers": ["Eritrea"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Baltic country which has produced 11 consecutive wife-carrying world champions", "correctAnswers": ["Estonia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Capital of the Canadian province of Alberta", "correctAnswers": ["Edmonton"], "difficulty": "insanely impossible" },
        { "question": "UK city with the world\’'s first municipal fire brigade", "correctAnswers": ["Edinburgh"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country with the highest incarceration rate in the world", "correctAnswers": ["El Salvador"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Iconic tower in Paris", "correctAnswers": ["Eiffel Tower", "Eiffel"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Continent that includes countries like Germany and Spain", "correctAnswers": ["Europe"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in East Africa with Addis Ababa as its capital", "correctAnswers": ["Ethiopia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. city in Texas known for being on the border with Mexico", "correctAnswers": ["El Paso"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Paraguayan City on the north bank of the Paraná River", "correctAnswers": ["Encarnacion"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        

    ],

    'F': [
        { "question": "Largest city in the interior region of Alaska", "correctAnswers": ["Fairbanks"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Scandinavia's \"Land of a Thousand Lakes\"", "correctAnswers": ["Finland"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Historic renaissance city in Italy", "correctAnswers": ["Florence"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Southern Japanese city of 1.6 million", "correctAnswers": ["Fukuoka"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "US state known for unusual news headlines and furries", "correctAnswers": ["Florida"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Danish territory with more sheep than people", "correctAnswers": ["Faroe Islands"], "difficulty": "hard" }, 
        { "question": "European country with the Louvre and the Eiffel Tower", "correctAnswers": ["France"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Oceanic island country", "correctAnswers": ["Fiji"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "US city home to the Historic Farmington Railroad Depot", "correctAnswers": ["Farmington"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Scandinavian country home to the first wife-carrying world champion", "correctAnswers": ["Finland"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Overseas collectivity home to Bora Bora", "correctAnswers": ["French Polynesia"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "National park on New Zealand's South Island ", "correctAnswers": ["Fjordland", "Fjordland national park”, “Fiordland"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Location of the start of the American Civil War", "correctAnswers": ["Fort Sumter Islands"], "difficulty": "hard" }, 
        { "question": "Capital city located in Tuvalu", "correctAnswers": ["Funafuti"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "U.S. state known as the Sunshine State", "correctAnswers": ["Florida"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "German city on the Main River", "correctAnswers": ["Frankfurt"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "French territory in South America", "correctAnswers": ["French Guiana"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in Australia near the Margaret River wine region", "correctAnswers": ["Fremantle"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "City in Texas with a large air force base", "correctAnswers": ["Fort Hood", "Fort Cavazos"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },

    ],
    'G': [
        { "question": "Port city in Scotland's western lowlands", "correctAnswers": ["Glasgow"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "African country whose capital is Conakry", "correctAnswers": ["Guinea"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country on the Caucasus Mountains", "correctAnswers": ["Georgia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Region in northwest Spain home to Lugo and Vigo", "correctAnswers": ["Galicia"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Cold desert in Mongolia and China", "correctAnswers": ["Gobi", "Gobi Desert"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "US state that borders Florida and home to Atlanta", "correctAnswers": ["Georgia"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Birthplace of Fanta, gummy bears, and accordions", "correctAnswers": ["Germany"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country in central Europe famous for beer, sausage, and the automotive industry", "correctAnswers": ["Germany"], "difficulty": "easy" }, 
        { "question": "Country home to the first olympics", "correctAnswers": ["Greece"], "difficulty": "medium" }, 
        { "question": "World's largest island", "correctAnswers": ["Greenland"], "difficulty": "medium" }, 
        { "question": "Danish territory in North America", "correctAnswers": ["Greenland"], "difficulty": "medium" }, 
        { "question": "Small mountain range in western Texas", "correctAnswers": ["Guadalupe", "Guadalupe Mountains"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country with the world's only natural nuclear reactor", "correctAnswers": ["Gabon"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Famous bridge located in California", "correctAnswers": ["Golden Gate Bridge"], "difficulty": "easy" }, 
        { "question": "1983 US invasion site known as the \”Spice Isle\”", "correctAnswers": ["Grenada"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country known for the Rock and as a British overseas territory", "correctAnswers": ["Gibraltar"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Island in the Caribbean known for its nutmeg", "correctAnswers": ["Grenada"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Largest city of the Isère department in the Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes region of southeastern France", "correctAnswers": ["Grenoble"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        {"question": "Region and city in western Ethiopia on the edge of the highlands", "correctAnswers": ["Gambela"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Russian republic in the Caucasus with capital city Nazran", "correctAnswers": ["Grozny"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },


    ],
    'H': [
        { "question": "U.S. state that Kauai is located in", "correctAnswers": ["Hawaii"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country where Tegucigalpa is located", "correctAnswers": ["Honduras"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Japan's north island", "correctAnswers": ["Hokkaido"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Seaside capital of Nova Scotia", "correctAnswers": ["Halifax"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Central European country home to the largest synagogue in Europe", "correctAnswers": ["Hungary"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. state that's the birthplace of superstar singer Bruno Mars", "correctAnswers": ["Hawaii"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital City that Camila Cabello has half of her heart in", "correctAnswers": ["Havana"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "City in Texas known for NASA and being the fourth largest in the U.S.", "correctAnswers": ["Houston"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Mountain range in Asia where Mount Everest is located", "correctAnswers": ["Himalayas"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "City in Germany known for its harbor and being a major port", "correctAnswers": ["Hamburg"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Historic city in Israel near the Mediterranean coast", "correctAnswers": ["Haifa"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where Honolulu is located", "correctAnswers": ["Hawaii"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "City in Northwestern Zimbabwe that is close to the international borders with Botswana and Zambia", "correctAnswers": ["Hwange"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Croatian island in the Adriatic Sea that is best known as a summer resort", "correctAnswers": ["Hvar"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Special administrative region of China known for its numerous skyscrapers", "correctAnswers": ["Hong Kong"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Coastal city that serves as the largest city and capital of the Red Sea Governorate of Egypt", "correctAnswers": ["Hurghada"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
    ],
    'I': [
        { "question": "Spanish island known for its nightlife and EDM", "correctAnswers": ["Ibiza"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country home to the world's most populous island", "correctAnswers": ["Indonesia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "City on the southern tip of New Zealand", "correctAnswers": ["Invercargill"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Turkish city formerly known by the Greek name of Smyrna", "correctAnswers": ["Izmir"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Russian city and oblast near Lake Baikal", "correctAnswers": ["Irkutsk"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. state containing the cities of Santa Claus and Gary", "correctAnswers": ["Indiana"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country home to bombardino crocodilo and tralalero tralala", "correctAnswers": ["Italy"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country home to Delhi and Mumbai", "correctAnswers": ["India"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "US state which produces the most corn", "correctAnswers": ["Iowa"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country which won the world cup in 2006", "correctAnswers": ["Italy"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country in Southern Europe that is shaped like a boot", "correctAnswers": ["Italy"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state known for its potatoes and mountain scenery", "correctAnswers": ["Idaho"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Greek island situated halfway between Naxos and Santorini", "correctAnswers": ["Ios"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital of the state of Enugu in Nigeria", "correctAnswers": ["Ikem"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "City in the Philippines located on the southeastern coast of the island of Panay", "correctAnswers": ["Iloilo City", "Iloilo"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Third-largest city by population in Nigeria", "correctAnswers": ["Ibadan"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Third largest town in Canada's Northwest Territories", "correctAnswers": ["Inuvik"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        
    ],
    'J': [
        { "question": "Saudi Arabian port city on the Red Sea", "correctAnswers": ["Jeddah"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Largest city in South Africa", "correctAnswers": ["Johannesburg"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Indian metropolis known as the Pink City", "correctAnswers": ["Jaipur"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Capital of the U.S.'s Last Frontier", "correctAnswers": ["Juneau"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country where the famous wonder of Petra is located", "correctAnswers": ["Jordan"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country in East Asia with cities like Osaka and Kyoto", "correctAnswers": ["Japan"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Major U.S. city in Florida known for its large population and the NFL mascot Jaguars", "correctAnswers": ["Jacksonville"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Island nation in the Caribbean known for reggae and beaches", "correctAnswers": ["Jamaica"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Island nation home to superstar Usain Bolt", "correctAnswers": ["Jamaica"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Island in Indonesia where Yogyakarta is located", "correctAnswers": ["Java"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Historic city in Israel that is sacred to multiple religions", "correctAnswers": ["Jerusalem"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "City in Afghanistan near the Pakistani border", "correctAnswers": ["Jalalabad"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in Yemen with a historic walled old town", "correctAnswers": ["Jibla"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Canadian national park located Northwest of Banff", "correctAnswers": ["Jasper", "Jasper National Park"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "island located in Northwestern Europe off the coast of Northwest France", "correctAnswers": ["Jersey"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Fifth-most populous city in Arkansas", "correctAnswers": ["Jonesboro"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
    ],

    'K': [
        { "question": "Country in the Middle East that shares its name with its capital", "correctAnswers": ["Kuwait"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Pakistani city with over 20 million people", "correctAnswers": ["Karachi"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Peninsula in Russia's far east", "correctAnswers": ["Kamchatka", "Kamchatka Peninsula"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital of Malaysia", "correctAnswers": ["Kuala Lumpur"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "City of over 4 million in northern Nigeria", "correctAnswers": ["Kano"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "African capital city with a population of roughly 16 million", "correctAnswers": ["Kinshasa"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. state known for fields, farms, and tornadoes", "correctAnswers": ["Kansas"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Asian peninsula split between two nations", "correctAnswers": ["Korea"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Major city in Missouri whose NFL mascot is the Chiefs", "correctAnswers": ["Kansas City"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "City in Japan known for its shrines and geisha culture", "correctAnswers": ["Kyoto"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Large city in Ukraine located on the Dnipro River", "correctAnswers": ["Kharkiv"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Mountainous region in Russia's far east with volcanic activity", "correctAnswers": ["Kamchatka"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in Nigeria with a population over 4 million", "correctAnswers": ["Kano"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Large industrial city in Kazakhstan with a population of roughly 500,000", "correctAnswers": ["Karaganda", "Karagandy"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Second highest mountain in the world located in Pakistan", "correctAnswers": ["K2"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Russian city near Mongolia that is on the Yenisei River ", "correctAnswers": ["Krasnoyarsk"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Second-largest city located in North Macedonia", "correctAnswers": ["Kumanovo"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        
    ],
    'L': [
        { "question": "Country in Europe that shares its name with its capital", "correctAnswers": ["Luxembourg"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country bordering Syria and Israel", "correctAnswers": ["Lebanon"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Second largest city and industrial hub of Papua New Guinea", "correctAnswers": ["Lae"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Country home to the former Barbary state of Benghazi", "correctAnswers": ["Libya"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Mining hub and second largest city in the DRC", "correctAnswers": ["Lubumbashi"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Highest capital city in the world", "correctAnswers": ["La Paz"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "European country where Riga is located", "correctAnswers": ["Latvia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. state with cities like Baton Rouge and New Orleans", "correctAnswers": ["Louisiana"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "German city famous for its trade fairs and classical music history", "correctAnswers": ["Leipzig"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. city where the Kentucky Derby is held", "correctAnswers": ["Louisville"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Canadian lake that shares a name with a common first name that is located in Alberta", "correctAnswers": ["Lake Louise", "Louise"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Historical province in southern France known for its lavender fields", "correctAnswers": ["Languedoc"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Tiny European microstate between Austria and Switzerland", "correctAnswers": ["Liechtenstein"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "River in Belgium that flows through the city of Liège", "correctAnswers": ["Lesse"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        
    ],
    'M': [
        { "question": "Country with the city of Marrakesh", "correctAnswers": ["Morocco"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital city of Nicaragua", "correctAnswers": ["Managua"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Largest research station in Antarctica, located on Ross Island", "correctAnswers": ["McMurdo Station", "McMurdo"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Microstate between Milan and Marseille", "correctAnswers": ["Monaco"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Major northwestern Russian city on the Barents Sea", "correctAnswers": ["Murmansk"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital of Liberia", "correctAnswers": ["Monrovia"], "difficulty": "hard"},
        { "question": "Country whose flag features an AK-47 crossed by a hoe", "correctAnswers": ["Mozambique"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "City in Michigan located on an island without cars", "correctAnswers": ["Mackinac Island"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where Detroit is located", "correctAnswers": ["Michigan"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state known for Minneapolis and the Twin Cities", "correctAnswers": ["Minnesota"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in Europe where capital city Valletta is located", "correctAnswers": ["Malta"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Island country known for a movie franchise starring King Julian", "correctAnswers": ["Madagascar"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country in Southeast Asia where capital city Kuala Lumpur is located", "correctAnswers": ["Malaysia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country in Central America where Mexico City is located", "correctAnswers": ["Mexico"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state with Jefferson City as its capital", "correctAnswers": ["Missouri"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "City in India known for Bollywood and a financial center", "correctAnswers": ["Mumbai"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Russian republic in the Caucasus", "correctAnswers": ["Magas"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Country in the Pacific where capital city Majuro is located", "correctAnswers": ["Marshall Islands"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        

    ],
    'N': [
        { "question": "U.S. state where Madison Square Garden is located", "correctAnswers": ["New York"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Indian island with virtually no contact with the rest of the world", "correctAnswers": ["North Sentinel Island", "Sentinel Island"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Largest city in Greenland", "correctAnswers": ["Nuuk"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Niger's capital", "correctAnswers": ["Niamey"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country home to Skopje", "correctAnswers": ["North Macedonia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Russian city located on the Ob River", "correctAnswers": ["Novosibirsk"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Russian city with the third largest population in the country", "correctAnswers": ["Novosibirsk"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Smallest island country by area", "correctAnswers": ["Nauru"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Northern region in Canada featuring polar bears and permafrost", "correctAnswers": ["Nunavut"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Town in Western Alaska known for dog sled races and permafrost tunnels", "correctAnswers": ["Nome"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "State where the geographic center of North America is located", "correctAnswers": ["North Dakota"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. state whose name means 'snow-covered' in Spanish", "correctAnswers": ["Nevada"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. state known for its corn and the city of Lincoln", "correctAnswers": ["Nebraska"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where Las Vegas is located", "correctAnswers": ["Nevada"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in southern Africa with capital city Windhoek", "correctAnswers": ["Namibia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country in Europe where Amsterdam is located", "correctAnswers": ["Netherlands"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in Central America where Managua is located", "correctAnswers": ["Nicaragua"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country in Oceania composed of many islands with capital city Alofi", "correctAnswers": ["Niue"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Modern capital city of Myanmar", "correctAnswers": ["Naypyitaw"], "difficulty": "hard" }
    ],
    'O': [
        { "question": "Capital city in the midwest of America", "correctAnswers": ["Omaha"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Notable waterfront city in northern Finland", "correctAnswers": ["Oulu"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country home to Muscat", "correctAnswers": ["Oman"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Canadian province with Thunder Bay and Sudbury", "correctAnswers": ["Ontario"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where Tulsa is located", "correctAnswers": ["Oklahoma"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state whose name starts and ends with the same letter", "correctAnswers": ["Ohio"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. city in Florida where Disney World is located", "correctAnswers": ["Orlando"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. state bordered by California and Washington", "correctAnswers": ["Oregon"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in Norway", "correctAnswers": ["Oslo"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Port city in southern Ukraine located on the Black Sea", "correctAnswers": ["Odesa"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Town in Iceland located near the mouth of the Ölfusá River", "correctAnswers": ["Olafsvik"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Japanese city on Honshu Island that was heavily bombed in WWII", "correctAnswers": ["Osaka"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Region in the Netherlands famous for cheese markets", "correctAnswers": ["Overijssel"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Ancient Greek city that hosted the original Olympic Games", "correctAnswers": ["Olympia"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "State in southern Mexico", "correctAnswers": ["Oaxaca"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Second-largest city in Kyrgyzstan, located in the Fergana Valley in the south of the country", "correctAnswers": ["Osh"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        

    ],    
    'P': [
        { "question": "Europe's largest rice growing region located in Italy", "correctAnswers": ["Po Valley", "Po Plain"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Landlocked South American country", "correctAnswers": ["Paraguay"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Brazilian state home to Curitiba", "correctAnswers": ["Parana"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City of 250,000 in northern Portugal", "correctAnswers": ["Porto"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Wonder of the world located in Jordan", "correctAnswers": ["Petra"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Point in the ocean farthest from land", "correctAnswers": ["Point Nemo"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country where Zamboanga Peninsula is located", "correctAnswers": ["Philippines"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "U.S. city that sits at the meeting of the Allegheny and Monongahela rivers", "correctAnswers": ["Pittsburgh"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in France", "correctAnswers": ["Paris"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in Europe where superstar Cristiano Ronaldo plays for", "correctAnswers": ["Portugal"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in South America home to capital city Lima", "correctAnswers": ["Peru"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Region in northwestern Pakistan", "correctAnswers": ["Peshawar"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Most populous city in Oregon", "correctAnswers": ["Portland"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Largest city located in Papua New Guinea", "correctAnswers": ["Port Moresby"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Mountain region located on the border of France and Spain", "correctAnswers": ["Pyrenees"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital of the Italian island of Sicily", "correctAnswers": ["Palermo"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital city of Transnistria, a breakaway region in Moldova", "correctAnswers": ["Tiraspol"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Russian city located on the Ural River near Kazakhstan", "correctAnswers": ["Penza"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Pennsylvania's largest city", "correctAnswers": ["Philadelphia"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        


    ],
    'Q': [
        { "question": "City in South America with a population of 2.8 million", "correctAnswers": ["Quito"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country in the Persian Gulf", "correctAnswers": ["Qatar"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Mexican state where Cancun is located", "correctAnswers": ["Quintana Roo"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Largest province in Canada by area", "correctAnswers": ["Quebec"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Australian state that is home of the Great Barrier Reef", "correctAnswers": ["Queensland"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Borough located in New York City", "correctAnswers": ["Queens"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "New Zealand city where the luge was invented", "correctAnswers": ["Queenstown"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Canadian city that is the capital of Quebec", "correctAnswers": ["Quebec City"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "City located in China's Shandong province on the Yellow Sea", "correctAnswers": ["Qingdao"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "City located in north-central Iran known for traditional architecture and desert landscape", "correctAnswers": ["Qom"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "City in Uzbekistan near the Aral Sea", "correctAnswers": ["Qarshi"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Guatemala's second-largest city", "correctAnswers": ["Quetzaltenango"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country in the Middle East with capital city Doha and rhymes with guitar", "correctAnswers": ["Qatar"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Contains Q: Country in West Asia that is bordered by Saudi Arabia to the south", "correctAnswers": ["Iraq"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "City located in the Phillipines on the Guadalupe Plateau, just northeast of Manila", "correctAnswers": ["Quezon,", "Quezon City"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in New Mexico with a population of over 560,000", "correctAnswers": ["Albuquerque"], "difficulty": "medium" },
    ],
    'R': [
        { "question": "African country bordering Uganda", "correctAnswers": ["Rwanda"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Baltic capital known for its medieval Old Town", "correctAnswers": ["Riga"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Sea separating the Middle East and Africa", "correctAnswers": ["Red Sea", "Red"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Smallest U.S. state", "correctAnswers": ["Rhode Island"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Famous road used for inspiration in the Disney Cars movies", "correctAnswers": ["Route 66", "66"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "South American City home of the famous Copacabana Beach", "correctAnswers": ["Rio", "Rio De Janeiro"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country home to cities such as Constanța and Brașov", "correctAnswers": ["Romania"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. state capital located in North Carolina", "correctAnswers": ["Raleigh"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "City in Nevada known for its casinos and slogan 'The Biggest Little City in the World'", "correctAnswers": ["Reno"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "The largest Indian state by area", "correctAnswers": ["Rajasthan"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in Virginia known for its history in the Revolutionary War", "correctAnswers": ["Richmond"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "City in central Russia located near the Volga River", "correctAnswers": ["Ryazan"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "River that flows through Laos, Thailand, and Cambodia before reaching Vietnam", "correctAnswers": ["Red River", "Red"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "River that flows through Baghdad and joins the Euphrates", "correctAnswers": ["River Tigris","Tigris"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "The largest of the Dodecanese islands of Greece", "correctAnswers": ["Rhodes"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "The largest country by area in the world", "correctAnswers": ["Russia"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "The largest country by area in the world", "correctAnswers": ["Rome"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Third largest city in Minnesota", "correctAnswers": ["Rochester"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" }
        
    ],
    'S': [
        { "question": "State in Australia with Alice Springs", "correctAnswers": ["South Australia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "South American country whose official language is Dutch", "correctAnswers": ["Suriname"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Italian island home to Palermo", "correctAnswers": ["Sicily", "Sicilia"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Yemeni island known for its unique dragon blood trees", "correctAnswers": ["Socotra", "Socotra Island"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Indonesia island with Makassar and Manado", "correctAnswers": ["Sulawesi"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Russia's largest republic, home to Yakutsk", "correctAnswers": ["Sakha", "Sakha Republic"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Norwegian archipelago home to Longyearbyen", "correctAnswers": ["Svalbard"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country with the most pyramids", "correctAnswers": ["Sudan"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country where the Paradise by Coldplay music video was filmed", "correctAnswers": ["South Africa"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Island nation named after a woman", "correctAnswers": ["St. Lucia", "Saint Lucia"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Country which contains the cities of Tambacounda and Kedougou", "correctAnswers": ["Senegal"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Chain of 11 uninhabited volcanic islands in the South Atlantic Ocean", "correctAnswers": ["South Sandwich Islands"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Island in the Aegean Sea famous for volcanic activity and whitewashed houses", "correctAnswers": ["Santorini"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Desert region that stretches across Arizona, California, and Mexico", "correctAnswers": ["Sonoran Desert"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country where capital city Stockholm is located", "correctAnswers": ["Sweden"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in Europe known for cities like Madrid and Barcelona", "correctAnswers": ["Spain"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Capital city in South America surrounded by the Andes and coastline", "correctAnswers": ["Santiago"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country in northeast Africa with capital Khartoum", "correctAnswers": ["Sudan"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country bordering west of Ethiopia", "correctAnswers": ["South Sudan"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country in the Balkans where NBA superstar Nikola Jokic is from", "correctAnswers": ["Serbia"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country in South America where capital city Paramaribo is located", "correctAnswers": ["Suriname"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Asian island nation known as the Teardrop of India", "correctAnswers": ["Sri Lanka"], "difficulty": "hard" },

    ],
    'T': [
        { "question": "Australian state that Cradle Mountain is located in", "correctAnswers": ["Tasmania"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Chinese region home to Lhasa", "correctAnswers": ["Tibet"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Malian city which was historically an important economic and academic center", "correctAnswers": ["Timbuktu"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Tech research center of over 200,000 in Norway", "correctAnswers": ["Trondheim"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Greece's second largest city", "correctAnswers": ["Thessaloniki"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country next to the Caspian Sea", "correctAnswers": ["Turkmenistan"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country where Red Bull originated", "correctAnswers": ["Thailand"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where Sandy Cheeks is from", "correctAnswers": ["Texas"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country with the province of Gorno-Badakhshan", "correctAnswers": ["Tajikistan"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "South American lake shared by Peru and Bolivia", "correctAnswers": ["Titicaca"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where capital city Austin is located", "correctAnswers": ["Texas"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where capital city Nashville is located", "correctAnswers": ["Tennessee"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in East Africa where Mount Kilimanjaro is located", "correctAnswers": ["Tanzania"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country where capital Tunis is located", "correctAnswers": ["Tunisia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country in Central Asia where capital city Dushanbe is located", "correctAnswers": ["Tajikistan"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. city in Arizona known for its desert and the University of Arizona", "correctAnswers": ["Tucson"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Village in the Arctic Inuvik region of Canada", "correctAnswers": ["Tuktoyaktuk"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in Japan", "correctAnswers": ["Tokyo"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "City in Georgia (the country) with a population of over 1.2 million", "correctAnswers": ["Tbilisi"], "difficulty": "hard" },
    ],
    'U': [
        { "question": "City in southern Argentina known as the gateway to Antarctica", "correctAnswers": ["Ushuaia"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "The secondary capital of Sweden, historically", "correctAnswers": ["Uppsala"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "South American country home to Salto and Punta del Este", "correctAnswers": ["Uruguay"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country home to Kyiv and Lviv", "correctAnswers": ["Ukraine"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country with the most traffic lights", "correctAnswers": ["United States", "US", "USA", "Freedom"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital of the Russian Bashkortostan republic", "correctAnswers": ["Ufa"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Cuntry associated with the Bald Eagle", "correctAnswers": ["United States", "US", "USA"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state known for the Great Salt Lake", "correctAnswers": ["Utah"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "South American country where capital city Montevideo is located", "correctAnswers": ["Uruguay"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Country in Central Asia with capital Tashkent", "correctAnswers": ["Uzbekistan"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in Sweden historically considered its secondary capital", "correctAnswers": ["Uppsala"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Country in the Middle East where Ajman is located", "correctAnswers": ["United Arab Emirates", "UAE"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country made up of England, Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland", "correctAnswers": ["UK", "United Kingdom"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country home to the most olympic medals", "correctAnswers": ["US", "United States"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "A massive sandstone monolith in the Northern Territories of Australia", "correctAnswers": ["Uluru"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Town referred to as Bali's culture capital", "correctAnswers": ["Ubud"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in Mongolia", "correctAnswers": ["Ulaanbaatar"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "South African town located on the banks of the Orange River", "correctAnswers": ["Upington"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Largest and busiest motion picture and TV studio in the world featuring a theme park in Orlando Florida", "correctAnswers": ["Universal", "Universal Studios"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Provincial capital city in northeast Thailand", "correctAnswers": ["Udon Thani"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },

    

    ],  
    'V': [
        { "question": "Largest city in British Columbia", "correctAnswers": ["Vancouver"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Fishing village in southern Iceland", "correctAnswers": ["Vik"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Seaside port and resort city on the Bulgarian coast", "correctAnswers": ["Varna"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Italian city with canals instead of roads", "correctAnswers": ["Venice"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Waterfall in Africa between two Z named countries", "correctAnswers": ["Victoria Falls", "Victoria", "Victoria Waterfall"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where Norfolk is located", "correctAnswers": ["Virginia"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state where the capital city of Montpelier is located", "correctAnswers": ["Vermont"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in Southeast Asia with capital Hanoi", "correctAnswers": ["Vietnam"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Contains V: U.S. city in Nevada known for its casinos", "correctAnswers": ["Las Vegas"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in South America where Caracas is located", "correctAnswers": ["Venezuela"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in Liechtenstein", "correctAnswers": ["Vaduz"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "The most populous city in the baltic states of Europe", "correctAnswers": ["Vilnius"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Island nation located in the South Pacific Ocean consisting of over 80 islands", "correctAnswers": ["Vanuatu"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in Austria", "correctAnswers": ["Vienna"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Australian province where Melbourne is located", "correctAnswers": ["Victoria"], "difficulty": "hard" },
    ],
    'W': [
        { "question": "Sits near the North Island's southernmost point in New Zealand", "correctAnswers": ["Wellington"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. state known for its cheese and beer", "correctAnswers": ["Wisconsin", "packers suck"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Appalachia's 'Mountain State'", "correctAnswers": ["West Virginia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Australian state with Bunbury, Geraldton, and Port Hedland", "correctAnswers": ["Western Australia"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. state that's the home of Devils Tower ", "correctAnswers": ["Wyoming"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in the Otago region of New Zealand known for a famous tree", "correctAnswers": ["Wanaka"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        {"question": "Mountain with the highest summit in the lower 48 states", "correctAnswers": ["Whitney"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "U.S. capital city that is not part of any state", "correctAnswers": ["Washington D.C.", "Washington DC"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "U.S. state that borders Oregon", "correctAnswers": ["Washington"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in the UK where the Welsh language is spoken", "correctAnswers": ["Wales"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "U.S. state with the capital city of Cheyenne", "correctAnswers": ["Wyoming"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in Poland", "correctAnswers": ["Warsaw"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in Western Germany known for its suspended monorail", "correctAnswers": ["Wuppertal"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "U.S. state bordered by Virginia and Ohio", "correctAnswers": ["West Virginia"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Disputed territory on the northwest coast of Africa primarily occupied by Morocco", "correctAnswers": ["Western Sahara", "West Sahara"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "U.S. city in Washingon known for its exquisite wine", "correctAnswers": ["Walla Walla", "Walla-Walla"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "City in Kansas known for aviation and aerospace industry", "correctAnswers": ["Wichita"], "difficulty": "medium" },
    ],
    'X': [
        { "question": "Largest city in the world starting with X", "correctAnswers": ["Xiamen"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Vast Chinese territory home to Urumqi and Turpan", "correctAnswers": ["Xinjiang"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Capital of Mexico's Veracruz", "correctAnswers": ["Xalapa"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital of Shaanxi Province in central China", "correctAnswers": ["Xi'an"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Contains X: Country containing the cities of Villahermosa and Tampico", "correctAnswers": ["Mexico"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Contains X: European country where the cities of Remich and Vianden are located", "correctAnswers": ["Luxembourg"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Contains X: Capital city in the Southwestern United States", "correctAnswers": ["Phoenix"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Contains X: U.S. state which the Armadillo and Longhorn are state mammals", "correctAnswers": ["Texas"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Contains X: U.S. state where Dallas is located", "correctAnswers": ["Texas"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Chinese autonomous region known for the Taklamakan Desert", "correctAnswers": ["Xinjiang"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Mexican archaeological site famous for pre-Columbian pyramids", "correctAnswers": ["Xochicalco"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Contains X: North American country bordering the U.S. to the south", "correctAnswers": ["Mexico"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Contains X: City home to a world-class college located in the United Kingdom", "correctAnswers": ["Oxford"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Contains X: Major port city in Tunisia located southeast of Tunis", "correctAnswers": ["Sfax"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Contains X: Second largest city in Kentucky", "correctAnswers": ["Lexington"], "difficulty": "medium" },

    ],
    'Y': [
        { "question": "Merida is located in this Mexican region", "correctAnswers": ["Yucatan"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Canadian province with a potato variety named after it", "correctAnswers": ["Yukon"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Myanmar's largest city", "correctAnswers": ["Yangon"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital of Cameroon", "correctAnswers": ["Yaounde"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Siberian city home to the Mammoth Museum", "correctAnswers": ["Yakutsk"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in Iran known for its ancient underground water systems", "correctAnswers": ["Yazd"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Contains Y: U.S. state that is home to Yellowstone and Cheyenne", "correctAnswers": ["Wyoming"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Country in the Middle East bordering Saudi Arabia and Oman", "correctAnswers": ["Yemen"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Contains Y: U.S. state that is home to Yellowstone and Cheyenne", "correctAnswers": ["Wyoming"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in Armenia", "correctAnswers": ["Yerevan"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. national park known for its geysers and hot springs", "correctAnswers": ["Yellowstone"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Historic city in Japan home to ancient temples and shrines", "correctAnswers": ["Yamaguchi"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "City in northern India in the state of Haryana", "correctAnswers": ["Yamunanagar"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Japanese city known for ceramic arts", "correctAnswers": ["Yokkaichi"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "National park in the Sierra Nevada mountains of California", "correctAnswers": ["Yosemite"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Walled city in northeast England founded by the ancient Romans", "correctAnswers": ["York"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Island in Micronesia that is also Gen Z slang", "correctAnswers": ["Yap"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Capital city of Canada's Northwest Territories", "correctAnswers": ["Yellowknife"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "U.S. state home to Times Square", "correctAnswers": ["New York"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Third most populous city in the U.S. state of New York", "correctAnswers": ["Yonkers"], "difficulty": "medium" },
    ],
    'Z': [
        { "question": "City on the Croatian coast in between Zagreb and Split", "correctAnswers": ["Zadar"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Archipelago off the coast of Tanzania", "correctAnswers": ["Zanzibar"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Country home to Harare and Bulawayo", "correctAnswers": ["Zimbabwe"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Dutch province whose 'New' version is more famous", "correctAnswers": ["Zeeland", "Zealand"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "African country whose capital is Lusaka", "correctAnswers": ["Zambia"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "City in Iran known for its Zoroastrian heritage", "correctAnswers": ["grandmaster"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "African country home to Victoria Falls", "correctAnswers": ["Zimbabwe"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in Switzerland", "correctAnswers": ["Zurich"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Longest east flowing river in Africa", "correctAnswers": ["Zambezi"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Ukrainian city that is Europe's largest nuclear power plant", "correctAnswers": ["Zaporizhzhia"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Third largest island in the Ionian Sea located off the west coast of Greece", "correctAnswers": ["Zakynthos", "Zante"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Capital of northeastern Spain's Aragon region", "correctAnswers": ["Zaragoza"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Resort town in southern Poland located at the base of the Tatras Mountains", "correctAnswers": ["Zakopane"], "difficulty": "grandmaster"},
        { "question": "Contains Z: Country with capital city of Brasília and the Amazon Rainforest", "correctAnswers": ["Brazil"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Contains Z: Former official name of Eswatini", "correctAnswers": ["Swaziland"], "difficulty": "hard" },
        { "question": "Capital of east-central China's Henan province", "correctAnswers": ["Zhengzhou"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Second most populous city in the Mindanao Province of The Phillipines", "correctAnswers": ["Zamboanga", "Zamboanga City"], "difficulty": "grandmaster" },
        { "question": "Southwest Utah nature preserve distinguished by canyons and steep red cliffs", "correctAnswers": ["Zion"], "difficulty": "medium" },
        { "question": "Capital city located in Croatia", "correctAnswers": ["Zagreb"], "difficulty": "medium"},
        { "question": "Contains Z: U.S. state home to cities such as Phoenix and Tucson", "correctAnswers": ["Arizona"], "difficulty": "easy" },
        { "question": "Contains Z: Country where Belize City is located", "correctAnswers": ["Belize"], "difficulty": "easy" },
    ]
};

export default questionBank;